

 \times

leninesteban98@outlook.co



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



Lenin4LP.github.io/Portfolio_LP



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



github.com/Lenin4lp

SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML



React

Bootstrap

LANGUAGES

Spanish

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

English

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

INTERESTS

VideoGames Dev

Web Dev

Lenin Patiño

Software Developer

I am a highly motivated Ecuadorian software developer with a specialization in web development. I hold a degree in Software Development Technology and have successfully developed multiple websites. I am passionate about learning and always strive to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies in the field.

FORMATION

Advanced Technology in Software Development Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Tesis:

 Developed a virtual tour for Lev Vygotsky School

EXPERIENCE

Administrative Assistant Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Fast Food Restaurant

Achievements/Responsabilities

- Administrative Assistant
- Logistics
- Teamwork

Contact: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

ORGANIZACIONES

Global Tour Group (06/2023 - Presente)

Co-founder

CERTIFICATES

SUDEN Certificate: Expert in computer, mobile phone, and printer repair.

(04/2023 - 05/2023)

SUDEN Certificate: Technical specialization (04/2023 - 05/2023)

SUDEN Certificate: International Technical Expert (04/2023 - 05/2023)

PERSONAL PROYECTS

Sitio web E-Commerce (06/2023 - Presente)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Top graduate of the Software Development program

Sangolquí, Ecuador.

Sangolqui, Ecuador



Lenin Patiño

Desarrollador de Software

Soy un desarrollador de software ecuatoriano altamente motivado, especializado en desarrollo web. Poseo un título en Tecnología en Desarrollo de Software y he creado exitosamente varias páginas web. Me apasiona aprender y siempre me esfuerzo por mantenerme actualizado con las últimas tecnologías en el campo.



leninesteban98@outlook.co m



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



Lenin4LP.github.io/Portfolio_LP



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



twitter.com/4fourlp? t=jgeNASSGNviB9dRdULaQB Q&s=09



github.com/Lenin4lp

COMPETENCIAS

JavaScript

HTML



React

Bootstrap

IDIOMAS

Spanish

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

English

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

FORMACIÓN

Tecnología Superior en Desarrollo de Software Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Tesis:

 Desarrollo de un tour virtual para el colegio Lev Vygotsky Sangolquí, Ecuador.

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Auxiliar Administrativo Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Fast Food Restaurant

Achievements/Responsabilities

- Auxiliar administrativo
- Logística
- Trabajo en Equipo

Contacto: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

Sangolqui, Ecuador

ORGANIZACIONES

Global Tour Group (06/2023 - Presente)

Co-fundador

CERTIFICADOS

Certificado SUDEN: Experto en reparación de computadoras, celulares e impresoras (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Certificado SUDEN: Especialidad Técnica (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Certificado SUDEN: Experto Técnico Internacional (04/2023 - 05/2023)

PROYECTOS PERSONALES

Sitio web E-Commerce (06/2023 - Presente)

INTERESES LOGROS

Desarrollo de videojuegos

Desarrollo web

Mejor egresado de la carrera de desarrollo de Software